Guide to the Wells Fargo Steinbeck Collection, 1892-1981
Department of Special Collections
- Series 4. John Steinbeck Letters to Family, 1910-1968
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1950 Feb. 16 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA ] n.d. [1950 Mar.] (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA ] n.d. [1950 Mar. - Apr.] (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], The Ritz-Carlton, Boston, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA Monday [1950 Oct. 2] (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA ] n.d. [1950 Oct.] (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1950 Dec. 17 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA [1950] Dec. 19 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1950 Dec. 25 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Somerset, Bermuda, to Esther and Carroll [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1951 Jan. 1 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1951 Jan. 27 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA ] 1951 Mar. 2 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, Siasconset, MA, to Esther and Carrol Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1951 July 14 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA ] n.d. (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1952 Sept. 9 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - APCS
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA [1952 Oct. 7] (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - APCS
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1952 Oct. 16 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - APCS
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1952 Nov. 10 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to "Dear Girls," n.p. n.d. [1952 Dec.] (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - TLS, 2 pp.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to "Dear Girls," n.p. 1953 Jan. 17 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - TLS (carbon), 3 pp. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1953 Feb. 27 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - John Steinbeck, n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA ] 1953 Summer (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - TLS, 4 pp.
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Mary [Dekker], Esther [Rodgers], Beth [Ainsworth], Watsonville, CA 1953 Nov. 2 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - TLS (carbon), 3 pp. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Paris, to "Kids" [Mr. & Mrs. E. R. Dethlefsen], n.p. 1954 June 27 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - TLS (with holographic note), 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1957 Jan. 18 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Italy], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1957 Mar. 8 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - TLS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Gibraltar, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1957 Apr. 3 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Firenze, Italia], to Esther [Rodgers] and all there, n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1957 May 3 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - TLS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], Florence, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1957 May 10 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - TLS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Roma, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1957 May 21 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - TLS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Stockholm, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1957 July 3 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - TLS, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1957 Summer (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - TLS (with holographic note), 2 pp.
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, NY, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1957 Aug. 12 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - TLS, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, NY, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1957 Aug. 22 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - TLS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], San Francisco, to Ed [Dethlefsen], n.p. n.d. [1957 Sept.] (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], Beth [Ainsworth], Mary [Dekker], Watsonville, CA 1957 Sept. 17 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - TLS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1957 Dec. 16 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - TLS, 2 pp. + envelope + 2 clippings
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] n.d. [1957 Dec. 22] (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - TLS, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Mrs. Radcliffe, n.p. [Salinas, CA] 1957 Dec. 22 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - TL (carbon), 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1957 Dec. 30 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - TLS, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1958 Jan. 9 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - TLS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Miami Beach, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1958 Jan. 25 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], Beth [Ainsworth], Mary [Dekker], Watsonville, CA 1958 July 2 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - TLS (carbon), 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, NY, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA] n.d. [1958 Fall] (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - TLS (fragment), 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], Beth [Ainsworth], Mary [Dekker], Watsonville, CA 1958 Nov. 20 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - TLS, 3 pp. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA ] n.d. [1959 Jan.] (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - ALS, 2 pp.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], Beth [Ainsworth], Mary [Dekker], Watsonville, CA 1959 Feb. 20 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - TLS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, Bruton, Somerset, England, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1959 Mar. 22 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - TLS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Bruton, Somerset, England, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1959 Apr. 13 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Bruton, Somerset, England], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1959 June 27 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - ALS, 3 pp. (1 leaf)
  - John Steinbeck, Bruton, Somerset, England, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1959 Aug. 10 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - ALS, 3 pp. (1 leaf)
  - John Steinbeck, Bruton, Somerset, England, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1959 Sept. 10 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Bruton, Somerset, England, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA Monday [1959 Sept. 28] (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], London, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA [1959] Oct. 7 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], Mary [Dekker], Beth [Ainsworth], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] n.d. [1959 Nov.] (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - TLS, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1959 Nov. 24 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - TPC
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA [1959 Dec. 8] (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - APCS
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, NY, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1959 Dec. 31 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - TPCS
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA [1960] Jan. 11 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], Charlotte Amalie, [St. Thomas, USVI], to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1960 Jan. 23 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], Charlotte Amalie, St. Thomas, USVI, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1960 Feb. 1 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1960 Feb. 15 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - TLS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1960 Feb. 17 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Sag Harbor, NY], to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1960 Aug. 29 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther and Carroll Rodgers, Watsonville, CA Two days after Xmas [1960 Dec. 27] (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - APCS
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers], Beth [Ainsworth], Mary [Dekker], Watsonville, CA 1961 Jan. 28 - 29 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - TLS, 2 pp. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Barbados, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1961 Feb. 25 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Sag Harbor, NY], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] Thursday [1961 May 14] (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - ALS, 2 pp.
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA Sunday [1961 Aug. 27] (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - ALS, 2 pp. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], London, to Esther [Rodgers], Beth [Ainsworth], Mary [Dekker], Watsonville, CA 1961 Oct. 2 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Dublin, to Esther [Rodgers], Beth [Ainsworth], Mary [Dekker], n.p. 1961 Oct. 16 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Dublin, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1961 Oct. 17 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - ALS, 3 pp.
  - [John Steinbeck], Milan, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1961 Dec. 3 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Florence, to "My dear Sisters," Watsonville, CA 1961 Dec. 17 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Rome, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1962 Jan. 9 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Capri, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1962 Jan. 26 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - TLS, 2 pp.
  - [John Steinbeck], Capri, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1962 Jan. 29 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, Capri, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA Friday [1962 Feb. 16] (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, Capri, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1962 Mar. 8 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Capri, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1962 Apr. 12 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, Athens, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1962 May 11 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Aboard the m.n. Saturnia, to Beth [Ainsworth], Esther [Rodgers], and Mary [Dekker], n.p. n.d. [1962 June 10 - 11] (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1962 June 25 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA Tuesday [1962 Aug. 21] (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Sag Harbor, to Esther [Rodgers], Beth [Ainsworth], and Mary [Dekker], n.p. Saturday [1962 Sept. 1] (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - ALS, 3 pp.
  - [John Steinbeck], Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA [1962 Sept. 2] (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] n.d. [1962 Fall] (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - ALS, 2 pp.
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Bubby and Ed [Dethlefsen], Portola Valley, CA 1962 Oct. 30 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1962 Nov. 14 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - APCS
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther [Rodgers] and Beth [Ainsworth], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] n.d. [1962 Dec.] (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - TLS, 2 pp.
  - Stockholm, Sweden. Nobel Speech. 1962 Dec. 10 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - TMs (carbon with holographic note), 2 pp.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1963 [Jan. 3] (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - ALS, 2 pp. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1963 [Jan. 7] (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], Sag Harbor, to Earl [Steinbeck], n.p. 1963 Jan. 28 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - ALS (facsim.), 2 pp.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1963 Jan. 31 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1963 Feb. 18 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1963 May 24 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - TPCS
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] n.d. [1963 July] (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - TL, 2 pp.
  - [John Steinbeck], Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1963 July 17 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p., to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] n.d. [1963 Summer] (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - ALS, 5 pp.
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1963 Sept. 18 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1963 Sept. 24 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], Moscow, to Esther [Rodgers], Beth [Ainsworth], and Mary [Dekker], n.p. 1963 Nov. 8 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - ALS, 3 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1963 Dec. 27 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1964 Feb. 3 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Sag Harbor], to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA Friday [1964 Feb. 28] (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA [1964] Feb. 29 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to All [Mrs. C.J. [Esther] Rodgers, et al.], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1964 Mar. 23 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - TLS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Roma, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1964 Apr. 4 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - ALS, 4 pp. (3 leaves) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Aboard Alitalia jet bound for Rome, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1964 Apr. 13 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1964 Apr. 24 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - APCS
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1964 May 10 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - APCS
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1964 May 18 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - TLS (with holographic note), 2 pp. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1964 June 9 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - APCS
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Mary [Dekker], Esther [Rodgers], and Beth [Ainsworth], Watsonville, CA 1964 June 22 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - TLS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1964 July 14 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - TPC
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1964 Aug. 14 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - TPC
  - [John Steinbeck], White House, Washington, DC, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1964 Aug. 24 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1964 Sept. 9 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - TPC
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1964 Oct. 1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - TL, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1964 Oct. 21 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - TPCS
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1964 Nov. 18 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], London, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1965 Jan. 8 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1965 Feb. 3 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - ALS, 2 pp.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1965 Feb. 17 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - TPC
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1965 Mar. 12 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers] and Beth [Ainsworth], n.p. 1965 Mar. 24 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - ALS, 3 pp. (2 leaves)
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1965 Apr. 13 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - ALS, 2 pp. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1965 Apr. 26 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - TPC
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1965 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - TPCS
  - John Steinbeck, n.p. [Sag Harbor], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] n.d. [1965 Summer] (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - ALS, 2 pp.
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1965 July 27 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - APCS
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1965 Aug. 11 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1965 Aug. 31 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - TPC
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers and Beth [Ainsworth], Watsonville, CA 1965 Oct. 8 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - TLS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1965 Oct. 21 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA Tuesday [1965 Nov. 9?] (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - ALS, 2 pp. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to "My dear Sisters," Watsonville, CA 1965 Nov. 17 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p., to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1965 Nov. 27 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], London, to Esther [Rodgers] and Beth [Ainsworth], Watsonville, CA 1965 Dec. 6 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - ALS, 4 pp. (2 leaves) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Dublin, to Esther [Rodgers] and Beth [Ainsworth], Watsonville, CA 1965 Dec. 19 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], St. Cleran's, Ireland, to Esther [Rodgers] and Beth [Ainsworth], Watsonville, CA [1965] Dec. 29 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Dublin, to Esther [Rodgers] and Beth [Ainsworth], Watsonville, CA 1966 Jan. 19 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck],Tiberias, Israel, to Esther [Rodgers] and Beth [Ainsworth], Watsonville, CA 1966 Feb. 17 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck],Haifa, Israel, to Esther [Rodgers] and Beth [Ainsworth], n.p. 1966 Feb. 19 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1966 Mar. 29 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - TPC
  - [John Steinbeck], Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA n.d. [1966 Apr. 14] (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1966 Apr. 15 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] [1966] May 19 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1966 June 6 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - TPCS
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1966 June 8 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - TPC
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1966 June 15 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1966 July 18 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA Monday [1966 July 25] (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - TPC
  - [John Steinbeck], Bangkok, to Esther [Rodgers] and Beth [Ainsworth], Watsonville, CA 1967 Jan. 29 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - ALS, 1 p. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA Monday [1967 Apr. 24] (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - APCS
  - John Steinbeck, White House, Washington, DC, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA Thursday [1967 May 11] (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1967 Sept. 20 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - TPC
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1967 Oct. 18 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - APCS
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1967 Dec. 6 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther [Rodgers] and Beth [Ainsworth], Watsonville, CA 1967 Dec. 15 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - ALS, 2 pp. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, Grenada, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1968 Jan. 6 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], St. Georges, Grenada, to Esther [Rodgers] and Beth [Ainsworth], Watsonville, CA 1968 Jan. 11 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1968 Jan. 29 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - TPC
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1968 Mar. 4 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Esther [Rodgers] and Beth [Ainsworth], Watsonville, CA 1968 Mar. 6 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - ALS, 2 pp. + envelope
  - John Steinbeck, n.p., to Esther [Rodgers], n.p. [Watsonville, CA] 1968 Mar. 26 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - John Steinbeck, Sag Harbor, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1968 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - TPC
  - John Steinbeck, New York, to Esther Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1968 Aug. 16 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Series 5. John Steinbeck Letters to Carolee Rodgers, 1926-1962
  - John Steinbeck, n.p., to [Esther Rodgers], n.p. n.d. [1926 Dec.] (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - ANS
  - [John Steinbeck], Svenska Amerika Linien, T.S. Drottningholm, to Caroline Rodgers, Watsonville, CA 1937 May 24 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Carolee Rodgers, Mills College, [Oakland], CA 1947 May 26 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Monterey, CA, to Carolee Rodgers, Oakland, CA 1948 Feb. 14 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - TL, 1 p. + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Carolee [Rodgers], n.p. [1948] June 18 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [Pacific Grove, CA], to Carolee Rodgers, n.p. n.d. [1948] (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - ALS, 1 p.
  - John Steinbeck, Pacific Grove, CA, to Carolee Rodgers, Berkeley, CA 1948 Nov. 25 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - ALS, 4 pp. (2 leaves) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], Pacific Grove, CA, to Carolee Rodgers, Berkeley, CA 1948 Dec. 3 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - APC
  - [John Steinbeck], Pacific Grove, CA, to Carolee Rodgers, Berkeley, CA 1948 Dec. 17 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - APC
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p., to Carolee Rodgers, n.p. n.d. [1949 Jan.] (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - AL, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + signed card
  - [John Steinbeck], Pacific Grove, CA, to Carolee Rodgers, Berkeley, CA 1949 Jan. 24 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - APCS
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p., to Carolee [Rodgers], n.p. [1949] Mar. 3 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], Chicago, to 'Sabrina' [Carolee Rodgers], Watsonville, CA 1949 Apr. 22 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf) + envelope
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Carolee [Rodgers], n.p. n.d. [1950 Mar.] (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], n.p. [New York], to Carolee [Rodgers], n.p. n.d. [1950 Mar.] (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - ALS, 2 pp. (1 leaf)
  - [John Steinbeck], New York, to Carolee Rodgers, Berkeley, CA Thursday [1950 Mar. 30] (Box 6, Folder 72)